Hello everyone, welcome to Wally Magazine. Today is...
大家好欢迎来到Wally Magazine今天是
February 28, 2026
2026年2月28日这是
The third piece of content is something everyone knows about the current US policy towards...
第三条片大家都知道现在美国对
Iran launched an attack and Israel
伊朗发动攻击和以
Israel together with Iran this time
色列一起而这次对伊
Lang's large-scale military action
朗大规模的军事行
The action means to completely overthrow
动是说要全面推翻
This regime, Trump is putting on a show.
这个政权特朗普出来演
This episode will be about Guangdong.
说今集就会是一个广东
Trump's voiceover was provided by
话的配音特朗普由
I've been counting and counting for a long time.
很久之前一直数一直数细
Why does he even believe that Iran...
数伊朗为什么他甚至认为
This war has the potential to create
今次的战争有机会造
He also caused casualties among American troops.
成美军的伤亡他也
There are a lot of people who would do that.
要这么做数了一大箩
The charges against him were brought to light and then he was called...
的罪状出来然后就叫伊
The Lang people reclaimed their country and he
朗人民夺回国家以及他也
Some say this military operation
有说今次军事行动
I will also consider the situation as follows.
的情况同样我会将我
The original English film is placed
英文原片的影片放在
You can check the information below.
下面资讯栏你们可以看回
His original English was...
他原本英文原装的
The statement is always in Cantonese.
说法因为始终广东话
We will try our best to achieve these voice-over results.
这些配音我们尽量做到
It's fairly accurate, but there's still a chance.
比较精准但是也有机会有
Let's not dwell on these discrepancies.
些偏差不要多说了去
Film We
片我们
The goal is to protect the United States
的目标是要保护美国
People eliminate the influence of Iranian politics
人民消除来自伊朗政
The urgent threat to power of this group
权的迫切威胁这班
Humans are an extremely vicious group
人是一班极之凶残
Very malicious people's threats
很恶毒的人他们的威胁
This behavior directly harms our department in the United States
行为直接危害美国我们的部
The team's overseas bases and we are still here
队海外基地还有我们在
Allies around the world for 47 years
世界各地的盟友47年
The Iranian regime has been shouting
来伊朗政权一直高叫
Down with the United States and endless campaigns
打倒美国发动无休止
Bloodshed and massacre
的血腥和大屠杀行
Our troops also have actions targeting the United States.
动针对美国我们的部队还有
Innocent citizens in many, many countries
很多很多国家的无辜市民
One of the earliest of these regimes
这个政权其中一个最早
The action is to support violent seizure
的行动就是支援暴力夺
Take the US Embassy in Texas
取美国大使馆在德克
Lan and his group kidnapped dozens of people
兰他们挟持了几十个
American hostages for a full 444 days
美国人质足足444天
Iran's proxy in 1983
1983年伊朗的代理
People launched an attack in Beirut
人在贝鲁特发动了
Marine Corps barracks explode
海军陆战队兵营爆
The bombing killed 241 people.
炸案杀死了241名
By 2000, American soldiers knew...
美国军人到了2000年他们知道
There is even a high chance of participating
甚至很大机会有份参
With the attack on the US Cowell destroyer
与攻击美国科威尔驱
Many of the destroyers did not survive the war.
逐舰很多人生还不了伊
Lang forces in Iraq
朗部队在伊拉克沙
The river merchant talked to hundreds of Americans
河商谈了几百名美国
Military as a proxy of the regime
军人这个政权的代理
People have continued to target China in recent years
人近年来继续对着中
The US military in the East launched numerous
东的美军发动无数
The attack also included US International Airlines.
次攻击还有美国国际航
Naval and sea routes
海路线上的海军和
Commercial ships are all affected by these
商业船只都中招这些
Large-scale terrorist acts we
大规模恐怖行为我们
Lebanon will no longer tolerate this.
再不会容忍下去由黎巴
So tender that Yemen from Syria
嫩到叶门从叙利亚
Until the regime in Iraq
到伊拉克这个政权一直
Armed training and funding of terrorism
武装训练和资助恐
terrorist militias command the entire
怖主义民兵令整个
The local bloodshed led to the uprising.
地方血流成河而发动
October 7th against Israel
10月7日对以色列
The brutal attack
的残暴袭击的正正
They are Iran's proxies.
就是伊朗的代理人哈
Musk killed over 1000
马斯杀了超过1000个
Innocent people include 46 Americans
无辜的人包括46个美国人
They also took 12 of our citizens hostage.
还挟持了我们12个公
The people being taken hostage is truly extreme
民做人质真是极度
I've never seen such a cruel world before.
残忍世界以前都没见过
Iran is the world leader in this matter.
这样的事伊朗是全球头
National-level terrorist support
号国家级恐怖主义支援
The person also recently took to the streets to protest
者最近还因为人民上街抗
He personally killed tens of thousands
议亲手杀了成万计
The United States has always been particularly concerned about its own citizens.
自己国民美国一直以来特别
My government insists on one political system
是我的政府都坚持一个政
The policy is this terrorist policy
策就是这个恐怖主义政
Power must never be possessed.
权绝对不可以拥有核
I'll say it again and again, they absolutely...
武我再讲多次他们绝
Therefore, it is forbidden to possess nuclear weapons.
对不可以拥有核武所以
Five nights in June last year
在去年6月的五夜
In Operation Hammer, we thoroughly
铁锤行动里面我们彻
The regime was completely destroyed.
底摧毁了这个政权在
Fordonatanz and I
福尔多纳坦兹和伊
Sfahan's nuclear program
斯法罕的核计划在
We warned after that attack
那次攻击之后我们警告
They should stop pursuing nuclear weapons.
他们不要再继续追求核武
I also tried to reach an agreement with them many times.
还多次尝试和他们达
We did our best to reach an agreement.
成协议我们尽力了他们
They want to do it, but they don't want to do it.
想这样做他们不想这样做
They reiterated their desire to do this.
他们再次表示想这样做他们
They didn't want to do this because they didn't know what was happening.
不想这样做他们不知道发生
What did they do? They just wanted to do evil.
了什么事他们只是想作恶
But Iran refused, just like
但是伊朗拒绝了就好像
They refused, just like they have for the past few decades.
过去几十年那样他们拒
All nuclear ambitions were abandoned.
绝了所有放弃核野心
We can no longer tolerate this opportunity.
的机会我们不能够再容忍
Instead of going down, they tried to go back.
下去了相反他们试图重
Nuclear construction plan and continued research and development
建核计划并继续研发
Research can pose a threat.
研究可以构成威胁的
Long-range missiles in Europe
远端导弹我们在欧洲
Good friends and allies stationed abroad
的好朋友和盟友驻外
The US military could even soon...
美军甚至很快就可以威
Imagine if it were to threaten the US mainland.
胁到美国本土你想想如果
This regime really possesses nuclear weapons.
这个政权真的拥有核武
They were also used to deliver their messages.
还用来传递他们的信
How arrogant they will be
息他们会多么有恃无
The US military may be acting for these reasons.
恐基于这些原因美国军方
A large-scale operation has already begun.
已经展开了一场大规
Model and continuous action
模而持续的行动去
Prevent this extremely evil and extreme
防止这个极邪恶极端
A dictatorial regime threatens the United States
的独裁政权威胁美国
And our core national security
和我们最核心的国家安全
We will take away their profits.
利益我们会抽起他们的
The missiles will be their missile workers
导弹将他们的导弹工
They will move the industry to the ground again
业移为平地他们会再
We will be completely wiped out next time.
次被彻底消灭我们会
We will annihilate their navy
歼灭他们的海军我们会
Ensure the terror in this region
确保这个地区的恐怖
The agent of ideology no longer has the ability
主义代理人再没有能
Force to undermine regional or global stability
力破坏地区或者世界稳
They must not attack us again.
定也不可以再攻击我们的
They can no longer use the military.
部队他们都不可以再用
homemade bombs or roadside bombs
土制炸弹或者路边炸
Sometimes this is called a serious bullet.
弹有时这样叫去严重
Injury and killing of thousands
伤害和杀害成千上
The tens of thousands of people, including many Americans, we
万的人包括很多美国人我们会
Ensure Iran cannot acquire nuclear weapons
确保伊朗拿不到核武
Information is very simple, they always
资讯很简单他们永远都
This regime will not have nuclear weapons.
不会有核武这个政权很
You'll soon understand that no one should be challenged.
快就会明白没有人应该挑战
The strength of the U.S. armed forces
美国武装部队的实力
And power, we have been in office for a long time
和威力我们在任期已经
Our military was established and rebuilt
建立和重建了我们的军
There is no army in the world.
队世界上没有任何军队
It can be compared with our military strength.
可以和我们的军力相比实
Our government's power or procedures
力或者先程序度我们的政府
We have done everything possible.
已经尽了一切可能措施
To reduce the number of US troops stationed in this area
去减低美国驻在这个地
Even so, the people in the district and I
区的人员即使如此而且我
It is not rash to say that Iranian politics
不是轻率地说伊朗政
Power is the courage to kill.
权是想杀人勇敢的
American heroes might sacrifice us.
美国英雄可能会牺牲我们
There may be casualties in the war.
可能会有伤亡战争里
These things happen from time to time, but
面这些事时有发生但
We did these things not for our present situation.
我们做这些不是为了现在我们
It's for the future.
是为了未来而做这是
A noble mission for us
一个崇高的使命我们为
Every soldier prays because
每一位军人祈祷因为
They selflessly risked their lives.
他们无私地冒着生命
Danger ensures Americans and our
危险确保美国人和我们的
The next generation will never be embraced
下一代永远不会受到拥
The threat of nuclear-armed Iran
有核武的伊朗威胁
We pray that God will protect all.
我们请求上帝保护所有
Heroes in peril
身处险境的英雄我们
I believe that with his help, the army
相信有他帮助军队里
Men and women in the noodles will definitely
面的男男女女一定会
We are the strongest in the world to win.
胜出我们有全世界最强
Their army will definitely win today.
的军队他们一定会赢今
Tonight I will talk to the Islamic Revolution
晚我要和伊斯兰革命
Guards, armed forces and all
卫队武装部队和所有
The police said you must put it down.
警察说你们必须放下
This way, the weapon can be fully unleashed.
武器这样就可以获得完全豁
Otherwise, one will have to face the inevitable
免否则就要面对必
The inevitable end was death, so they let it go.
死无疑的下场所以放
You will gain by disarming yourselves.
下你们的武器你们会获
They deserve fair treatment and complete freedom.
得公平对待和完全豁
Otherwise, one will have to face the inevitable
免否则就要面对必
In the end, I was certain of death.
死无疑的下场最后，我
Tonight I will be with the great and self
今晚要和伟大而自
The Iranian people say you are free.
豪的伊朗人民说你们自由
The moment has come to stay in safety
的时刻就来到留在安全
Do not leave your home.
的地方不要离开你们的家
It's dangerous outside, there will be bombs.
外面很危险，炸弹会
After we get everything sorted out...
到处落等我们搞定之后
You then take over your government.
你们就接管你们的政府到
The government at that time belonged to this possibility.
时政府就属于你们这个可能
This is the only time in your generations.
是你们几代人唯一一次
You've been looking for this opportunity for so many years
机会这么多年来你们一直要
You asked the US for help, but you never did.
求美国帮忙但你们从来
None of them have ever received a total
都没有得到过没有一个总
I'm willing to do it tonight.
统肯做今晚我愿意
What you're doing now is a total
做的事现在你们有一个总
The system truly gave you what you wanted.
统真的给了你们想要的
Let's see how you respond.
东西那就让我们看看你们怎样回
The United States should now use overwhelming force
应美国现在用压倒性的
Power and destructive weaponry
力量和毁灭性的武
Now is the time to give you the support you need.
力支援你们现在就是时候掌握
Your own destiny is about to be released
你们自己的命运释放近
Prosperity and light within reach
在咫尺的繁荣和光
Hui's future is now taking action.
辉未来现在是采取行
Don't let it roll away when it's moving.
动的时候不要让它滚走愿
God bless the U.S. Armed Forces
上帝保佑美国武装部
The brave male and female officers and soldiers of the team
队的勇敢男女官兵
God bless America
愿上帝保佑美利坚
United States of America, God bless!
合众国愿上帝保佑
Thank you for listening to Trump.
你们谢谢听完特朗普讲
After that, he will be here for so many years.
之后这次他将这么多年
Detailed reasoning over the past 47 years
47年以来的理据细
The numbers were counted, and even funding was provided.
数了出来甚至乎资助
Terrorism has become a
恐怖主义变成了一个
If a terrorist regime is
恐怖主义政权如果是
No wonder he said he didn't have it either.
这样的情况难怪他说他也没有
Underestimating Iran, even he
小看伊朗甚至乎他
I think there's a chance that American soldiers will be injured.
觉得有机会有美军的伤
Even in death, one must do this.
亡都要这样去做也呼
For 47 years, so many years have passed.
吁47年这么多年以来
The Iranian people are asking the United States for help, but
伊朗人民叫美国帮忙但是
This time it's the only one I can't get.
都得不到这次是唯一
It's a one-time opportunity, so everyone has their own opinion.
一次机会所以大家怎么看都各
There are different opinions, but Iran
有不同的看法但是伊朗
Did any of their allies help in this situation?
的盟友有没有在这次帮
Are you busy? Do you dare or not?
忙呢敢不敢呢还是这
If we don't help this time, will they come one by one?
次不帮忙会不会一个一个
Should we fall down or what? Perhaps everyone...
倒下还是怎样呢不如大家
Let's have a lively discussion about this below.
一起在下面热烈讨论这
That's all for today, see you next time!
次讲到这里了下次再见
Everyone has heard this far, I hope everyone...
大家都听到这里了希望大家
Like this video and share it with your friends.
like这条片share给朋友
Remember to subscribe! Thanks for watching, bye-bye!
记得要subscribe多谢收看拜拜